

PRENGKI ARDIANSYAH

"I CAN IF I WANT, AND IF ALLAH RIDHA"

PROFILE

I am Prengki Ardiansyah. I am 19 years old. I have an interest in being active in organizing. I have also various participated in organizationts when high scholl. And now, I wanna join to Badan Legislatif Mahasiswa (BLM) Politeknik Caltex Riau to continue my experince

CONTACK

- Jl. Yossudarso, Meranti Pandak, Rumbai
- prengki19si@mahasiswa .pcr.ac.id
- 0823 8559 9743

SKILL

- Leadership
- Communicating
- Team Work
- Critical Thinking
- Socialist

EDUCATION

ELEMENTARY SCHOOL

SDN 002 Pembatang

JUNIOR HIGH SCHOOL

MTs Hayatul Islamiyah Pangean

SENIOR HIGH SCHOOL

MAN 2 Kuantan Singingi (MANDAKU)

COLLEGE

Politeknik Caltex Riau

EXPERIENCE

- Vice chairman of OSIS MAN 2 Kuansing 2016 -2017 (Wakil Ketua OSIS)
- Chairman of OSIS MAN 2 Kuansing 2017 2018 (Ketua OSIS)
- Member of FOKSI (Forum OSIS Kuantan Singingi)
 2016 2018
- Head of the MANDAKU Scout troop 2016-2017 (Pradana Pramuka MANDAKU)
- Honorary Council of MANDAKU Scouts 2017-2018 (Dewan Kehormatan Pramuka MANDAKU)
- Provos of Marching Band Gita Satria MANDAKU 2018
- The head of the science class 3 Perkemahan Ilmiah Remaja Nasional 17th in Purbalingga (Ketua Kelas IPATEK 3 PIRN 17 Purbalingga)
- Mosque administrator Paripurna Mukminin (Pengurus Masjid Paripurna Mukminin)
- Field coordinator HI Sport for badminton in 2019 (Koor Lap HIMASISTIFO Sport cabang badminton)